interface QuizQuestionObj{
  id: number;
    quiz_img: string,
    question: string,
    options: string[],
    answer: string,
    anime: string,
    tag: string,
    difficulty: number,
}

export const quiz_questions: QuizQuestionObj[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    quiz_img: "url1",
    question: "Who is the main protagonist of Naruto?",
    options: ["Sasuke", "Naruto", "Sakura"],
    answer: "Naruto",
    anime: "Naruto",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 60,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    quiz_img: "url2",
    question: "In 'Death Note,' what is the main character's alias?",
    options: ["L", "Light Yagami", "Misa Amane"],
    answer: "Light Yagami",
    anime: "Death Note",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 75,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    quiz_img: "url3",
    question:
      "Which anime features a group of pirates searching for the One Piece?",
    options: ["Dragon Ball", "One Piece", "Attack on Titan"],
    answer: "One Piece",
    anime: "One Piece",
    tag: "Series",
    difficulty: 50,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    quiz_img: "url4",
    question:
      "What is the name of the giant humanoid creatures in 'Attack on Titan'?",
    options: ["Titans", "Giants", "Colossals"],
    answer: "Titans",
    anime: "Attack on Titan",
    tag: "Creature",
    difficulty: 70,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    quiz_img: "url5",
    question: "In 'My Hero Academia,' what is the main character's Quirk?",
    options: ["Explosion", "One For All", "Half-Cold Half-Hot"],
    answer: "One For All",
    anime: "My Hero Academia",
    tag: "Quirk",
    difficulty: 65,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    quiz_img: "url6",
    question:
      "Which anime features a high school club dedicated to finding supernatural phenomena?",
    options: [
      "Hyouka",
      "Steins;Gate",
      "The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya",
    ],
    answer: "The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya",
    anime: "The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya",
    tag: "Series",
    difficulty: 55,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    quiz_img: "url7",
    question: "What is the signature move of Goku in 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
    options: ["Kamehameha", "Spirit Bomb", "Final Flash"],
    answer: "Kamehameha",
    anime: "Dragon Ball Z",
    tag: "Technique",
    difficulty: 80,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    quiz_img: "url8",
    question:
      "In 'Sword Art Online,' what is the name of the virtual reality MMORPG?",
    options: ["Aincrad", "Alfheim", "GGO"],
    answer: "Aincrad",
    anime: "Sword Art Online",
    tag: "Game",
    difficulty: 70,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    quiz_img: "url9",
    question: "Who is the main character in 'Fullmetal Alchemist'?",
    options: ["Edward Elric", "Alphonse Elric", "Roy Mustang"],
    answer: "Edward Elric",
    anime: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 65,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    quiz_img: "url10",
    question:
      "What is the name of the ghost girl in 'Bleach' who guides souls to the afterlife?",
    options: ["Orihime", "Rukia", "Yoruichi"],
    answer: "Rukia",
    anime: "Bleach",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 60,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    quiz_img: "url11",
    question:
      "In 'Cowboy Bebop,' what is the name of the spaceship the main characters travel on?",
    options: ["Swordfish II", "Bebop", "Red Tail"],
    answer: "Bebop",
    anime: "Cowboy Bebop",
    tag: "Vehicle",
    difficulty: 75,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    quiz_img: "url12",
    question: "What is the power of Natsu Dragneel in 'Fairy Tail'?",
    options: ["Ice Magic", "Fire Dragon Slayer Magic", "Telekinesis"],
    answer: "Fire Dragon Slayer Magic",
    anime: "Fairy Tail",
    tag: "Magic",
    difficulty: 70,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    quiz_img: "url13",
    question: "Who is the creator of 'Neon Genesis Evangelion'?",
    options: ["Hayao Miyazaki", "Hideaki Anno", "Makoto Shinkai"],
    answer: "Hideaki Anno",
    anime: "Neon Genesis Evangelion",
    tag: "Creator",
    difficulty: 55,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    quiz_img: "url14",
    question: "What is the name of the demon fox sealed within Naruto?",
    options: ["Kurama", "Shukaku", "Matatabi"],
    answer: "Kurama",
    anime: "Naruto",
    tag: "Creature",
    difficulty: 65,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    quiz_img: "url15",
    question: "In 'One Punch Man,' what is Saitama's superhero name?",
    options: ["Genos", "Mumen Rider", "One Punch Man"],
    answer: "One Punch Man",
    anime: "One Punch Man",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 60,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    quiz_img: "url16",
    question:
      "Which anime is set in the world of alchemy and follows the Elric brothers?",
    options: [
      "Attack on Titan",
      "Fullmetal Alchemist",
      "My Hero Academia",
    ],
    answer: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
    anime: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
    tag: "Series",
    difficulty: 65,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    quiz_img: "url17",
    question: "What is the name of the robotic cat in 'Doraemon'?",
    options: ["Nobita", "Shizuka", "Doraemon"],
    answer: "Doraemon",
    anime: "Doraemon",
    tag: "Character",
    difficulty: 50,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    quiz_img: "url18",
    question:
      "In 'Demon Slayer,' what is the main character Tanjiro Kamado's weapon?",
    options: ["Katana", "Bow and Arrow", "Dual Swords"],
    answer: "Katana",
    anime: "Demon Slayer",
    tag: "Weapon",
    difficulty: 70,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    quiz_img: "url19",
    question: "Who is known as the 'Strongest Hero' in 'One Punch Man'?",
    options: ["Genos", "Saitama", "Mumen Rider"],
    answer: "Saitama",
    anime: "One Punch Man",
    tag: "Title",
    difficulty: 75,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    quiz_img: "url20",
    question:
      "What is the name of the magical school in 'Little Witch Academia'?",
    options: ["Hogwarts", "Luna Nova", "WizTech"],
    answer: "Luna Nova",
    anime: "Little Witch Academia",
    tag: "Location",
    difficulty: 55,
  },
];
